CHRISTOPHER MORROW

Cleveland OH, 44113

Phone: (567) 288-5538 | Email: Morrow7564@gmail.com LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/christopher-morrow-45b9a5167/

GitHub: https://github.com/morrow7564 | Portfolio: https://christophermorrow.herokuapp.com/

SUMMARY

Front-end web developer utilizing my growing expertise in creating fully responsive, interactive web applications. I have a vast knowledge and concentrated skills in responsive programming, while also attaining an understanding of server side web applications. As someone who has shown initiative, growth, leadership, and the ability to adapt quickly to the task at hand in past job roles, I will be a strong asset to any front-end development team.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Language/Libraries/Frameworks:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, SQL, Node.js, Express, MySQL, Sequelize, MongoDB, Mongoose, EJS, Handlebars, React, JSX, Git.

PROJECTS

Modern Living | Github.com/morrow7564/Mordern-Living | https://modernlive.herokuapp.com/

- An application used for writing notes which can be saved and deleted
- Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, Express

Budget Tracker| Github.com/morrow7564/SmartMoney | https://smartmoneybudget.herokuapp.com/

- A full-stack app used for tracking monthly transactions and bills to pay
- Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ¡Query, Node.is, Express, MySQL, Sequelize

Restaurant Finder | Github.com/morrow7564/Restaurant-Finder | https://morrow7564.github.io/Restaurant-Finder

- An app that helps you find and locate restaurants
- Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Ajax

EXPERIENCE

Assist Protection Telhio Credit Union

2020 – 2020 Columbus, OH

- Collected balances and worked with co-workers on getting settlements
- Efficiently utilized company resources to provide effective problem resolutions
- Flourished in a high volume fast paced environment.
- Worked independently and as part of a team to handle customer conflict and resolved issues professionally.

Financial Service Representative Telhio Credit Union

2018 – 2020 Columbus, OH

- Assist customers during the loan and account application process, and close consumer and real estate and mortgage loans in accordance with internal and federal policies and procedures.
- Helped new and existing clients open personal accounts, resolve issues related to online banking services.
- Analyzing financial data received from members to develop strategies for meeting client's financial goals

2016 – 2018 Columbus, OH

- Balance Automated Teller machines, Teller Cash Dispensers often totaling more than \$100,000 ∘ Opening new Accounts for new members
- Executed loan origination process, including ordering credit reports, appraisals, and title reports Underwriting for new loans
- Analyze applicants financial status, credit, and property evaluation to determine loan feasibility

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Certificate: Case Western University, Cleveland, OH A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

Finance Degree: University of Toledo, Toledo, OH